const geography = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "Which river flows through Paris?",
        answer: "river seine",
        hint: "Eventually flows to the English channel"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "In which country is the UK’s highest mountain, Ben Nevis?",
        answer: "scotland",
        hint: "This country covers the northern third of the island of Great Britan"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "Mount Vesuvius overlooks which modern Italian city?",
        answer: "naples",
        hint: "Also home to the Duomo di San Gennaro cathedral"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "What is the highest active volcano in Europe?",
        answer: "mount etna",
        hint: "Located on Sicily"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "Which European capital city is divided by canals into about 90 islands joined by about 400 bridges?",
        answer: "amsterdam",
        hint: "Cycling is a key part of this city"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "What’s the world’s biggest port?",
        answer: "port of shanghai",
        hint: "Over took Port of singapore to become the worlds bussiest"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Which South American country has land borders with ten other countries?",
        answer: "brazil",
        hint: "The largest South American country"
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "Which city is also known as ‘The Eternal City’?",
        answer: "rome",
        hint: "The capitol city of Italy"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "The Great Barrier Reef is off the coast of which Australian state?",
        answer: "queensland",
        hint: "The capitol is Brisbane"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "Which island would you Visit to kiss the Blarney Stone?",
        answer: "ireland",
        hint: "Formerly part of the United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "In which country would you be if you were Visiting the Taj Mahal?",
        answer: "india",
        hint: "The second most populus country in the world"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "In which Scandinavian country would you find fjords?",
        answer: "norway",
        hint: "Capitol city is Oslo"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "Which country’s name could be part of a Christmas dinner?",
        answer: "turkey",
        hint: "Capitol Ankara"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "Which stretch of water separates Anglesey and Wales?",
        answer: "menai strait",
        hint: "This strait is crossed in two places"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "In which continent is the world’s longest river, the Nile?",
        answer: "africa",
        hint: "The worlds second largest continent"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "What colour is the spot in the middle of the Japanese flag?",
        answer: "red",
        hint: "Symbolises the sun"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "Is Australia in the northern or the southern hemisphere?",
        answer: "southern",
        hint: "Water will flow counter clockwise here"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "What does each star on the flag of the United States stand for?",
        answer: "a state",
        hint: "There are 52 of these"
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: " Which bridge, one of the oldest roadway bridges in the United States, was completed in 1883 and spans the East River?",
        answer: "brooklyn bridge",
        hint: "Located in New York"
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: "On an O.S Map with a scale of 1:25000, how many inches represent one mile?",
        answer: "Two and a half",
        hint: "Similar to a famous american sitcom"
    }

];

export default geography;